io.com 2011-12-17

# Legal Policies, Rules & Regulations & Terms of Service - IO

This is the Website of IO Data Centers. 

Contact Information:  
IO Data Centers  
615 N. 48th St.  
Phoenix, AZ 85008  
866.382.6236

Your privacy and the security of your information are very important to us. This Privacy Policy governs the website(s) operated by IO Data Centers (collectively, our "Website"). It explains how we collect your information and the choices you have concerning the use and disclosure of such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Except as agreed upon as part of the Terms of Use or as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell, share, license, trade or rent your personal information collected on our Website to others. 

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on our Website. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. By using our Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by our Website. We are not responsible for the privacy of the information you reveal, allow access to or post in any public forum. 

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT**   
We collect two types of information: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. Our service providers also mass aggregates client data as part of its general business practices. This aggregated data is used to identify and analyze trends to improve our systems and to create derivative materials that may be marketed to potential clients and used to service current clients; it does not contain personally identifiable information regarding you. 

_Personally Identifiable Information_  
Personally identifiable information is information that identifies you and can be used to identify or contact individuals ("Personally Identifiable Information"). Such Personally Identifiable Information may include name, address, email, telephone number, birth date and other non-public information. If we collect Personally Identifiable Information, except as agreed to under the terms of our contract with you, if applicable, we will not sell, share, license, trade or rent your Personally Identifiable Information other than as specified in this Privacy Policy. When data is aggregated, we remove all personally identifiable information prior to use. 

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information_  
We also may collect information that cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information (such as age, profession, gender or reason for call) and physical information (area of call, general customer type). Non-Personally Identifiable Information may also include user IP address, browser types, domain names and other anonymous statistical data created by aggregating user information collected through the use of our Website. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is used to help us better understand the characteristics of the businesses that may use our services. We use the information collected and aggregated to improve and market our services to you and other businesses. In the event that we link any Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Personally Identifiable Information, we will treat such information as Personally Identifiable Information and only use such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

_Information from Other Sources_  
We also may supplement the information we collect with information from other sources to assist us in providing our services. In addition, we may use this supplemental information in evaluating and improving our services and to determine your preferences so that we can tailor our Website and services to your needs. Information obtained from other sources and compiled with your information by us is the sole property of IO Data Centers. 

**WHERE AND WHEN IS INFORMATION COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE**   
We may collect information (including Personally Identifiable Information) regarding you in different manners and at different places and times throughout our Website. The following is a description of the areas and/or manners in which we primarily collect information about you. 

_Becoming a Registered User_  
We may ask that you complete certain steps to become a registered user of the Website. In such instance, you may be required to provide us with information (including Personally Identifiable Information) such as your personal information or that of your company (e.g. name, business address, email address and information regarding your business). 

_Cookies and Action Tags_  
We also may collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information passively using cookies and action tags through our Website. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer in order to identify: (i) your Web browser; (ii) the activities of your computer on our Website; and (iii) your activity in connection with our marketing and promotional efforts. 

Cookies my be used to: (i) personalize your experience on our Website (e.g. to dynamically generate content on web pages specifically designed for you); (ii) assist you in using our services (e.g. to save you time by not having to reenter your name upon each visit to our Website); and (iii) allow us to statistically monitor how you are using our Website for purposes of improving our offerings. 

We may also use cookies to conduct marketing and promotional efforts, tailor certain advertisements to your browser that we think may be of interest to you, or to determine the popularity of certain content. 

You do not have to accept cookies to use our Website; however, you may not be able to use certain offerings, features or resources of our Website if you do not accept cookies. Although most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, you may reset your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to reject cookies generally. Most browsers offer instructions on how to do so in the Help section of the toolbar. 

Action tags, also known as web beacons or gif tags, are a web technology used to help track website usage information, such as how many times a specific page has been viewed. Action tags are invisible to you, and any portion of our Website or email sent to you on our behalf, may contain cookies that are associated with action tags that are located on our Website. Unlike cookies, action tags are not placed on your computer. 

We may select and use different third parties from time to time to track website usage through action tags on our Website and on our advertisements on other websites. 

If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an email to [info@iodatacenters.com](mailto:info@iodatacenters.com) or by calling us at 866.676.5901. 

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailing, please let us know by sending us an email at the email address above or calling us at the phone number above. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us an email at the email address above or by calling us at the phone number above.

back to top
